birzeit.edu 2018-06-29

# Privacy & Cookies Policy | Birzeit University

##  **Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Birzeit University (BZU) collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users of Birzeit University’s website ([www.birzeit.edu](http://www.birzeit.edu/)) and its sub-sites. This privacy policy applies only to Birzeit University’s main website (this website) and its sub-sites indicated by the subsite_name.birzeit.edu domain. Websites of institutions, units, and faculties within the university may issue their own privacy policy information; otherwise, this policy will be inherited and applied.

**1.1 Personal information**

BZU may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways and situations, including, but not limited to, when users visit the website, register on the website, respond to a survey, and fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources BZU makes available on the website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, names, email addresses, mailing addresses, and phone numbers. BZU will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information.

**1.2 Usage information**

BZU may collect and store web usage information when users use the website. This information may include:

  * IP address
  * Requested URL
  * Referring URL
  * Data and time of page visits
  * Software information, such as the browser and operating system used
  * Internet access domain name

**1.3 Web browser cookies**

A cookie is a small file, which asks permission to be placed on a device’s local storage. The BZU website uses cookies that are issued to recognize browser sessions and enhance the user experience. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but users can usually modify their browser settings to decline cookies or alert them when cookies are being sent; however, doing so may prevent them from taking full advantage of the website and some parts of the website may not function properly.

**1.4 How we use collected information**

The university may use and analyze the information collected to maintain this website, develop its functionality and content, and improve future services. The university will not store or associate any such analytical data with personally identifying information. BZU only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and the data is then removed from BZU systems.

**1.5 Personal information privacy**

BZU is committed to protecting user privacy. Should BZU ask users to provide certain information by which they can be identified when using this website, those users can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. BZU will not sell, trade, or rent user personal information to any third parties without user permission or are required by law to do so.

**1.6 Third party websites**

This website may contain links to external websites (pages that do not belong to the [.birzeit.edu](http://www.birzeit.edu/) domain). These sites are not controlled by the university and hence are not governed by this privacy policy.

**1.7 Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The university reserves the right to update its Privacy Policy from time to time. Any future updates will be posted here. Check this page from time to time to stay abreast of any changes.

**1.8 Contact Information**

For additional information and queries about the above Privacy Policy, please contact:

  * Public Relations Office
  * Email: [pr@birzeit.edu](mailto:pr@birzeit.edu). Tel: +972 (02-2982000)

##  **Copyright**

All materials and content on this website are reserved by right to Birzeit University. This includes pictures, graphs, charts, logos, and other designing material. It is prohibited to copy, disseminate, or reproduce all or part of the materials in any form or by any means without the prior written permission of Birzeit University has concerned department and if the following conditions are met:

  1. Copies are not made or distributed for commercial or advertising use
  2. The BZU copyright, its date and a notice providing that permission for copying was granted by BZU, appear on the reproduced materials, with link to unit’s website

Some materials may require additional copyright permission from the author(s).

**For further information, contact:[webmaster@birzeit.edu](mailto:webmaster@birzeit.edu)**

© Birzeit University
